export default data = [
  {
      question: "It rained so hard yesterday that the baseball game had to be _______ until next Saturday.",
      options: ["surrendered","postponed","abandoned","opposed"],
      correct_option: "postponed"
  },
  {
      question: "As more people rely on the Internet for information, it has _______ newspapers as the most important source of news.",
      options: ["distributed","subtracted","replaced","transferred"],
      correct_option: "replaced"
  },
  {
      question: "Having saved enough money, Joy _______ two trips for this summer vacation, one to France and the other to Australia.",
      options: ["booked","observed","enclosed","deposited"],
      correct_option: "booked"
  },
  {
      question: "Since I do not fully understand your proposal, I am not in the position to make any _______ on it.",
      options: ["difference","solution","demand","comment"],
      correct_option: "comment"
  },
  {
      question: "Betty was _______ to accept her friend’s suggestion because she thought she could come up with a better idea herself.",
      options: ["tolerable","sensitive","reluctant","modest"],
      correct_option: "reluctant"
  },
  {
      question: "The bank tries its best to attract more customers. Its staff members are always available to provide _______ service.",
      options: ["singular","prompt","expensive","probable"],
      correct_option: "prompt"
  },
  {
      question: "John’s part-time experience at the cafeteria is good _______ for running his own restaurant.",
      options: ["preparation","recognition","formation","calculation"],
      correct_option: "preparation"
  },
  {
      question: "Women’s fashions are _______ changing: One season they may favor pantsuits, but the next season they may prefer miniskirts.",
      options: ["lately","shortly","relatively","constantly"],
      correct_option: "constantly"
  },
  {
      question: "Standing on the seashore, we saw a _______ of seagulls flying over the ocean before they glided down and settled on the water.",
      options: ["pack","flock","herd","school"],
      correct_option: "flock"
  },
  {
      question: "The book is not only informative but also _______ , making me laugh and feel relaxed while reading it.",
      options: ["understanding","infecting","entertaining","annoying"],
      correct_option: "entertaining"
  },
  {
      question: "After working in front of my computer for the entire day, my neck and shoulders got so  _______ that I couldn’t even turn my head.",
      options: ["dense","harsh","stiff","concrete"],
      correct_option: "stiff"
  },
  {
      question: "Getting a flu shot before the start of flu season gives our body a chance to build up protection against the _______ that could make us sick.",
      options: ["poison","misery","leak","virus"],
      correct_option: "virus"
  },
  {
      question: "The kingdom began to _______ after the death of its ruler, and was soon taken over by a neighboring country.",
      options: ["collapse","dismiss","rebel","withdraw"],
      correct_option: "collapse"
  },
  {
      question: "Though Kevin failed in last year’s singing contest, he did not feel _______ . This year he practiced day and night and finally won first place in the competition.",
      options: ["relieved","suspected","discounted","frustrated"],
      correct_option: "frustrated"
  },
  {
      question: "Emma and Joe are looking for a live-in babysitter for their three-year-old twins, _______ one who knows how to cook.",
      options: ["initially","apparently","preferably","considerably"],
      correct_option: "preferably"
  },
]
